Register of the F. Ryan Duffy Papers, 1906-1979
Wisconsin Historical Society
- General Correspondence, 1933-1973
  - V.I.P. Correspondence, 1933-1952
    - Congress
      - 1933-1938 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - 1933-1938 (continued) (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Government, 1933-1938 (Box 23, Folder 2-4)
- Speeches, 1934-1969
  - 1934-1937 May (Box 23, Folder 5-9)
  - 1937 June-September (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 1937 October (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1938 January-May (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 1938 June (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1938 July-August 8 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1938 August 10-October 8 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 1938 October 10-November (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 1939 March-1940 May (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 1941 June-1957 February (Box 25)
  - 1957 April-1965 November (Box 26)
  - 1966 March-1971 January (Box 27)